寿星  你准备好了吗
Hey, birthday girl. You ready?
记住明天有降级培训  是规定的
Remember de-escalation training tomorrow, mandatory.
真是美好的周六啊  谢谢你
Oh, it's my dream Saturday. Thank you.
不是你一个人  伯吉斯  我们都得去
Not all about you, Burgess. We all gotta be there.
别说这个了
Let's jump this joint.
姑娘们  今天可是周五
Ladies, it's Friday night.
我们去莫利酒吧做一点坏坏的决定
Let's get to Molly's and make some bad decisions.
我们回头就去
I think we're right behind you.
说到坏决定  寿星
Speaking of bad decisions, birthday girl,
你准备好一年一度的射击了吗
are you ready for these annual Malort shots?
不行  今年不行
That's a negative. It's a low-key event this year.
再说了  兰德尔得了流感  要早睡
Besides, Randall has the flu, gonna make it an early night.
那不是问题  我要去一趟巴克镇
No problem with that. I gotta make a quick run to Bucktown.
是吗  要我一起吗
Yeah? You want me to come with?
不用  莫利酒吧见
Uh-uh. Uh, meet you at Molly's.
-好吧  -我听说
- Okay. - Okay, so I heard
奥蒂斯说服了赫尔曼
that Otis convinced Herrmann to put
在莫利酒吧放了一台卡拉OK机
a karaoke machine in at Molly's.
真是个烂主意
Bad idea.
会吸引一些乌合之众
Attracts the wrong kind of crowd.
我不知道  可能会很好玩
I don't know, could be really fun.
不可能的  伯吉斯
When pigs fly, Burgess.
*我告诉你那很蠢*
*Let me tell you it's always cool*
*老板有时候并不介意*
*And the boss don't mind sometimes*
*你表现得像个傻子*
*If you act a fool*
*就在洗车店*
*At the car wash*
你是下一个  安东尼奥  唱辛纳特拉的怎么样
You're next, Antonio. How about a little Sinatra?
那也太老了吧  我找找别的
That's grandpa music. I'll find something.
-真的吗  -对
- Seriously? - Yeah.
你知道董事长
You understand the majesty
拥有绝对权威吧
of the Chairman of the Board, right?
杰  听我说话
Jay, come back.
我想听《夏天的风》
I wouldn't mind hearing a little "Summer Wind."
凯文  你去哪了  快过来
Kev! Hey, man, where you at? Get down here.
-快过来  -我们都在这里
- Come down here! - We're all here.
快来
Get down here.
还是语音信箱
It keeps going to voicemail.
他会来的  别担心
He'll be here, don't worry.
举起手来
Let me see your hands.
别动
Don't move.
别紧张  好吗
Just take it easy, a'ight?
别动
Don't move.
听着
Listen, man.
是时候赎罪了
Time to pay for your sins.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十二集
-抱歉  -你迟到了
- Sorry. - You're late.
我知道  我会补考的
I know. I'll do the make-up test.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我在找凯文
I--I was looking for Kev.
-他不在家里吗  -不在
- Any luck at his house? - No.
邮件也没收  床也没动过
Mail's untouched, his bed's still made.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   Lynn_宁   H小欠
但他的车不在家里  似乎他没回去过
But he's car's not there so it looks like he never came home.
也没来这里
And he's a no-show for this.
翻译     小萝莉   不高兴童鞋   圈圈
我们追踪一下他  特鲁迪
Let's track him down. Trudy.
定位他的手机  从那里开始
Ping his direct connect phone. Start there.
昨晚上他说他要
Hey, so listen, last night he said he had
校对     圈圈
去巴克镇办事情
to take care of something in Bucktown.
他有和你提过相关的事情吗
He ever mention anything like that to you?
-没有  -有乔丹和凡妮莎的消息吗
- No. - Anything about Jordan and Vinessa?
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
没有
No.
是吧  我上次听说时  他们都还挺好的
Right? I mean last time I heard, they were doing great.
后期     8T
我好像找到他了
Hey, I think I got him.
手机信号在罗斯伍德
Phone's pinging from Rosewood.
总监     圈圈
北十四街4458号
4458 North 14th Street.
那离巴克镇很远
That's a long way from Bucktown.
冷的
It's cold.
-看起来完好无损  -这在这里可不容易
- Doesn't look damaged. - Small miracle in this hood.
再强悍的轮胎在这条街也会被搞爆胎
Hellcat wheels go for 400 a pop on the street.
他来这里做什么
What was he doing here?
找到他的手机了
Got his phones.
私人用机已经关机了
His personal's dead.
找到一个地址
Got an address.
4458.
就是这里
That's right here.
G5021  我需要查找
5021 George. Squad, I need a name associated
和北十四街4458号有关的信息
with an address: 4458 North 14th Street.
稍等
Standby.
-找到什么了吗  -乔·贝克
- You find anything? - Got a Joe Baker.
两项前科  一次伤害罪
Two priors for delivery, one assault.
阿特沃特提过一个住在这里的乔·贝克吗
Atwater ever mention a Joe Baker, felon that lives here?
-我查一下  -没有  怎么了
- I got the back. - No, why? What's going on?
在车里找到了这个人的地址  看看他在不在家
Found his address in the car. Let's see if he's home.
怎么回事
What the hell?
海莉
Hailey.
-安全  -安全
- Clear. - Clear.
安全
Clear.
-金  我开门了  -好
- Kim, I'm opening the door. - Okay!
有发现吗
Anything?
这里有血
I got blood here.
什么
What?
是阿特沃特的警徽和身份证件
It's Atwater's badge and ID.
警校他们教你的第一件事就是
First thing they tell you in the Academy.
当罪犯拿枪指着你  你就丢掉身份证件
Offender gets a gun on you, you dump your ID.
不能告诉他们你是警察
You never tell 'em you're a cop.
好吧  那...
All right, so...
罪犯在这里袭击了阿特沃特
Offender attacks Atwater in here.
他丢掉了警徽
He dumps his star.
然后他把他弄出去了
Then he walks him outside.
阿特沃特最后收到的
Last thing Kevin got was a few messages
是一个叫米歇尔的女人发给他的消息
from a woman named Michelle.
她在等他的消息
She was waiting to hear from him.
让普拉特追踪她
Have Platt track her down.
车库锁了  在外面找到了这个
Garage was padlocked. Found this inside.
半块可卡因砖
Half a brick of coke.
所以乔·贝克又重操旧业了
So Joe Baker's back dealing again.
有人想敲他
Someone tries to rip him off?
结果阿特沃特被抓住了
And Atwater got caught in the middle of it.
对  但阿特沃特一开始
Yeah, but what the hell was Atwater doing here
到底为什么来这里
in the first place?
也许他是来追踪一条线索的
Maybe he got a lead and was trying to make a bust.
但那样的话他不会一个人来  我们都知道的
But he wouldn't go in alone. We all know that.
好吧  我们继续从乔·贝克身上入手
All right. Let's keep digging into Joe Baker.
找出他和阿特沃特的联系
Find the connect between him and Atwater.
海莉  过来
Hailey, come over here.
大家都过来  听着
Everybody come over here. Listen up.
这件事暂时先保密
I want to keep this in-house for now.
如果消息泄露出去  他们就会知道凯文是警察
Look, this leaks? They find out Kevin's a cop,
那他就死定了
he's a dead man.
还有别的消息吗
All right, what else we got?
我们发现乔·贝克
All right, so we found out that Joe Baker,
昨天没去上班
he didn't show up to work yesterday.
他和凯文之间有联系吗
Any connections between him and Kevin?
没有  阿特沃特没和他接触过
No, Atwater didn't make any of Baker's pinches.
他也不在线人名单里
He's not on any CI rolls.
好  他给凯文打过电话或者发过短信吗
All right, any calls or texts to Kevin?
没有  贝克最后的联系人
No, no. Baker's last communication was
是一个叫凯尔文·希尔的人
a series of texts between him and a guy named Calvin Hill.
-希尔有前科吗  -没有  干净的
- Hill have a sheet? - No, he's clean.
好吧  我们去找希尔  要快
Okay, so we find Hill. Fast.
凯尔文·希尔
Calvin Hill.
我是道森警探
I'm Detective Dawson.
这是我的搭档伯吉斯  你认识叫乔·贝克的人吗
This is my partner Burgess. You know a guy named Joe Baker?
认识  怎么了
Sure do. Why? What's going on?
我们在找他  你看到他了吗
We're looking for him. Have you seen him?
你和他说过话吗
Have you spoken to him?
我们周四一起喝的酒
Thursday we had drinks together.
-你怎么认识他的  -我们一起在后院教练
- How you know him? - We coach at the Y together.
你有没有见过他
You ever seen him with this guy?
不  不认识这家伙
No, don't know that guy.
等等  你是说乔不见了
Wait, are you telling me that Joe's missing?
-是的  周四失踪的  -你上次见到乔时
- Yes, since Thursday. - Last time you saw Joe,
他有没有表现得很紧张  好像害怕某人似的
was he acting nervous? Scared of anybody?
不  我们只是在斯莱德酒吧聊天
No, we were just catching up at the Slide Bar.
整晚酒吧只有你们两个人吗
Okay, so it was just you two at the bar all night?
基本上是的
For the most part.
然后他勾搭上一个小美女  他们就一起走了
Then he met this little honey and they left together.
-知道她的名字吗  -索尼娅什么的
- You catch her name? - Sonya something.
问完了吗  我得去上班了
Look, are we done? I gotta get to work.
嗯  待在城里  凯尔文
Yeah, just stay in town, Calvin.
我不会去哪儿的
I'm not going anywhere.
我刚和实验室的麦蒂森谈过了
I just talked to Mattison at the lab.
贝克客厅的血迹和阿特沃特相符
The blood in Baker's living room is a match to Atwater.
警长  我们有发现
Sarge, we got something.
我一直在监视乔·贝克的社交媒体
I've been monitoring Joe Baker's social media.
这是刚发布的
This just got posted.
听着  听我说
Listen. Listen to me.
我没有  伙计
I ain't got it, man.
别这样
All right, come on.
-他在那里  -这是报复
- There he is. - This is payback.
这是匿名发布的  标题《复仇》
It was posted anonymously. Screen name "Venganza."
-意思是复仇  -资料是假的
- Means revenge. - This profile's fake.
这个账号是专门用来发布这个视频的
It was created just to post this.
好了  那至少有两名犯人
All right, we know we got at least two offenders.
一个摄像  另一个人打
There's one guy filming, and one guy doing the beating.
找技术人员分析这段视频
All right, let's get some OCD techs on this right away.
-找个信得过的人  -我认识一个
- I want someone we can trust. - I got a guy.
很好  找他  埃尔  安东尼奥
Good, use him. Al, Antonio.
去每个拉丁帮派敲打敲打
You shake down every Latino gang,
和乔·贝克有关的贩毒团伙
drug crew associated with Joe Baker.
再放一次
All right, run it again.
-锁定那个拳头  -好的
- Freeze on that fist. - Okay.
那是面墨西哥旗  黑帮风格的
It's a Mexican flag, gangster style.
看看能不能找到能辨认出的东西
All right, see if it pops with any of our knowns.
看看那些窗户  彩色玻璃
Look at the windows. Stained glass.
-教堂吗  -有可能
- Yeah. Church? - Could be.
算是有所发现
Well, it's better than nothing.
-好消息是他还活着  -没错
- Good news, he's alive. - Yeah.
必须要让他继续活着
And he's gonna stay that way.
小声点  伙计
Hey, yo. Keep it down, man.
他们会回来的
They'll come back.
你对他们做了什么
What the hell did you do to them?
我什么都没做  好吗
I ain't do nothin' to them. All right?
我这辈子从来没见过那些人
I never seen them before in my life.
伙计  你现在还有心思耍我吗
Man, you think now is a good time to play me, fam?
如果你拿了他们的货
Huh? If you got their dope,
还给他们  伙计  这不值得
just give it back. Man, this ain't worth it.
你怎么回事  你是聋了还是怎么的
The hell's wrong with you? You deaf or something, man?
我刚说什么来着
What'd I just say?
我不认识他们
I don't know them,
我没有拿他们的货  好吗
and I ain't got their dope, a'ight?
我早就不干了
I'm out of the game.
我假释后就干净了
I've been clean ever since I made parole.
伙计  我们唯一的机会就是
Come on, man. Only chance we got is
你面对事实  乔  就这样
if you own up to the truth, Joe, that's it.
你还和我
Don't you talk to me
说什么面对事实
about owning up to no truth, a'ight?
-你才需要面对  -现在不行  不行
- You need to do that. - Not now, not now.
乔  现在不行  伙计
Come on, Joe. Not now, man.
我感觉我和杀死我儿子的混蛋
I feel like I'm in hell being chained up with the bastard
一起被锁在地狱里
who murdered my son.
-警长  -什么事
- Sergeant. - Yeah?
有几件事
A couple of things.
霍斯特德找的技术人员说
According to Halstead's guy at OCD,
脸书发布源查不到什么
the Facebook post is a dead end.
-IP地址加密了  -好的
- The IP address is encrypted. - All right.
但是我对乔·贝克的调查倒是有些发现
I had more luck digging into Joe Baker.
发现他和阿特沃特有关系
Found a connection between him and Atwater.
那是罗尼·卡特赖特
That is Ronnie Cartwright.
五年前  罗尼抢劫了西区的一家便利店
Five years ago Ronnie robs a 7-Eleven in West Lawn.
他杀了一名柜员  整个过程都被摄像头拍下来了
He kills the clerk, the whole thing is caught on video,
-罗尼逃走了  -阿特沃特抓住了他
- and Ronnie's on the lam. - Atwater made the arrest.
阿特沃特当时在巡查
Yeah, Atwater was conducting a canvas,
看到罗尼正从一个工地中出来
sees Ronnie coming out of the housing projects.
罗尼开始逃跑  阿特沃特堵住了他
Ronnie runs. Atwater corners him.
罗尼拔出了枪  就此被击毙
Ronnie pulls a gun. Good-bye Ronnie.
你当时在场吗
Were you there?
我离得很近  但我没看到
I was close, but I didn't see it.
但当时有很多证人
But there were a lot of witnesses.
阿特沃特接受了圆桌会议  隐私管理  内务调查
And Atwater went through the Round Table, IPRA, IAD,
只要你想得到  都裁定开枪是正当的
you name it. It was ruled a good shoot.
好吧  我信
Okay, I'll bite.
这和乔·贝克有什么关系
What's this got to do with Joe Baker?
关系大了
Everything.
-怎么了  -我们找到了米歇尔
- What's up? - We found Michelle,
昨晚给阿特沃特发短信的女孩
the girl that messaged Atwater last night.
她是乔·贝克的妹妹
She's Joe Baker's sister.
带她过来
Bring her in now.
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
你不知道怎么回事
You have no idea what's going on?
我说了
Like I just told you,
我打给凯文是因为我担心我哥哥
I called Kevin 'cause I was worried about my brother.
-他失踪了...  -我们知道
- He's been missing-- - Yes, we know.
他的假释官昨天打给你
His parole officer called you yesterday.
说乔一次见面没去  你去了他家
Joe missed a meeting. You went by his house.
他不在  你打给他
He wasn't there. You called him.
-他不接  我们知道  -我明白
- He's not answering. We know. - Okay, I get it.
你很害怕
You're scared.
-为什么不报警  -我报警了
- Why not call the police? - I did.
警车根本没来
The car never showed.
抓我们的时候来得可真快
They get here fast to arrest us,
我们需要帮助的时候却不见影子
not so much when we need help.
你为什么要打给杀死你侄子的人
Why would you call the guy who killed your nephew?
这件事不怪凯文
I don't blame Kevin for what went down.
我爱罗尼
I loved Ronnie.
但我知道他是个怎样的孩子
But I knew what kind of kid he was.
总是想混黑帮
Always trying to be a gangster.
谁的话都不听
Wouldn't listen to nobody.
凯文总是说如果我需要找人就找他
And Kevin always said if I needed something to call.
-于是我就找了他  -因为你担心
- So I did. - Because you were worried
乔惹上了黑帮的人
about Joe being in trouble with gangbangers?
不
No.
-他早就不混了  -他没有不混
- He's out of the game. - He ain't out of the game.
我们在乔的车库找到了一公斤可卡因
We found a half a kilo of cocaine in Joe's garage.
什么
What?
-不  那不...  -米歇尔
- No. That can't be ri-- - Michelle.
你知道乔和谁在合作吗
Do you know who Joe was running with?
不  不  他不贩毒了
No. No. He's not dealing anymore.
我了解我哥哥
I know my brother.
这  这不可能
This isn't--this isn't making any sense.
你认识有这个纹身的人吗
You know anyone with that tattoo?
-不认识  -你确定吗
- No. - You sure?
我说了我不知道
Look, I'm telling you I don't know.
你的枪真不错
You packing quite a cohete.
你不是条子吧
You ain't a cop, are you?
什么条子  我是保安
Cop? I'm a security guard.
格洛克17  芝加哥警局标准配枪
Glock 17 CPD's bread and butter.
我不知道啊哥们  我老大给我的枪
I don't know about that, man. My boss gave me a gun.
我说谢谢你  就拿着用了
I said thank you. I kept on moving.
-你叫什么  -安东尼
- What's your name? - Anthony?
安东尼
Anthony.
我只想要回我的货  安东尼
I just want my product returned, Anthony.
我靠这个养家
This is how I feed my family.
我说了  我这里没有
I told you. I don't have it.
那就抱歉了
I'm sorry to hear about that.
别啊哥们  真的不是我  好吗
Come on, man. I'm not the guy, okay?
那你之前在他家干什么
What were you doing over at his house then?
我过去是因为周五要和他
I was going over there to just meet up
碰个头
with him on a Friday night.
-碰头干什么  -玩啊  我们是哥们
- To do what? - To hang out. We homeys.
-哥们  -是啊
- Homeys? - Yeah.
我那天晚上在他家被抢时他那个哥们
You the same homey that was with him the other night
就是你吗
I got jacked at his house?
我说了  你说的什么我根本不知道
I already told you, I don't know nothing about that.
钱拿来了
Yo, got the cash.
戴了个面具
Wore a mask.
拿了多少
How much you pull?
300  把乔的卡刷爆了
300. Maxed out Joe's card.
但你仔细看小票
But check out the receipt.
没想到他这么有钱
You richer than you look.
天啊  存了一万九
Damn. 19 G's in the savings?
你一分钱都别想拿到
Yeah, and you ain't getting none of that.
是吗
No?
那钱是市里给我的
The city gave me that money
是补偿我儿子的事的
for what they did to my son.
是和解金  我就只剩这些了
It's a settlement. And it's all that I have left.
所以你想拿钱  就先杀了我吧
So you're gonna have to bury me before I give it up.
-你确定吗  -绝对确定
- Yeah, you sure about that? - Yeah, I'm damn sure--
你想怎么死  轮不着你来说
You don't tell me how it's gonna be.
周一早上  你和我去银行
Monday morning, you and me, we going to the bank.
你把那一万九都取出来
And you're gonna take out all 19,000.
为防着你做傻事  我们会带把铁锨的
We'll bring a shovel just in case you're feeling stupid.
好的  多谢
Okay, got it. Thanks.
大家听好了
All right, listen up.
资产查收部查到了
Asset Forfeiture got a hit
乔·贝克借记卡
on Joe Baker's debit card.
这些监控照片仍然是从西坪的
These surveillance stills are from a walk-up ATM
街头提款机上拍的
in West Lawn.
这个面具男去了300块
This guy with a max took out 300 bucks.
把乔的每日限额刷爆了
Maxed out Joe's daily limit,
但是账户里还剩一万九
but he still got over 19 grand in the account.
-什么时候的事  -三小时前
- When was this? - Three hours ago.
那如果他们想拿钱的话  那很可能
So, if they're after money, there's a good chance
他们会等周一去把钱取光
they're gonna wait until Monday and wipe out the account.
那我们还有36小时
Well, that leaves us 36 hours.
那好  杰  厄普顿
All right, Jay, Upton,
去西坪这个提款机附近查一查
head over to West Lawn to this ATM.
查一查附近商户的监控摄像
Check PODS, surveillance of nearby businesses.
没准能看到这个骷髅男在附近停的车
Maybe we catch Skeletor parked somewhere close.
你确定你没事吗
Hey, you sure you okay?
这也不是我第一次中枪了
It ain't the first time I've been shot.
你
And you...
我猜你作为警察  这种事天天见吧
I bet you see this all the time, being police.
毫无来由地就开枪打人
Shooting brothers for no reason.
我认识这么两个人
You know, I know two people
当晚就在外面
that were out there that night.
他们两个都说
Both of them say...
罗尼根本就没有试图掏枪
Ronnie never tried to grab a gun.
-连手都没动  -不  不
- He never even reached for it. - No. No.
你把罗尼像条野狗一样打死了
You shot Ronnie like he was a damn dog.
你把他害死了
You put his ass in the ground.
你根本不知道当时什么情况  大哥
You don't know what the hell happened, man.
我知道  我当然知道
Yes, I do. I damn sure do.
市里赔给我两万
The city paid me 20 G's.
这就证明你就是个杀人凶手
That shows and proves you a damn murderer.
我猜你大概想都不会再想一下了吧
I bet you don't even think about it again.
我杀了一个年轻黑人  乔
I killed a young black male, Joe.
没错  你杀了
Yeah, you did.
你根本不知道这对我影响有多大
You have no idea how much that affects me.
你以为我当警察就为了能杀人吗
Think I became a cop so that I could kill people, man?
而且还是我自己人  我们说的可是罗尼
Especially not my own people. We talking about Ronnie.
得了吧
Yeah, right.
罗尼跟我出身在一片街区
Ronnie's from the same place I'm from.
拜托大哥  我天天都在想那孩子
Come on, man. I think about that boy damn near every day.
我晚上一闭眼就能看到他的脸
He one of the last faces I see when I shut my eyes at night.
你知道我还想到了谁吗
And you know who else I think about?
被他杀了的那个前台
That clerk he murdered.
你知道他的名字吗
You even know his name?
你在乎吗
Do you even care?
米卡尔·沙马迪
Mikal Shamardi.
他上了牙医学校  他还有个妻子
He was also in dental school. He also had a wife.
她名字叫金柏莉  他们未来的日子
Her name was Kimberly, and they had a bright future
本来一片大好  结果你儿子
ahead of 'em before your son
为了三百多块钱  把它夺走了
came and took it for $312.
那个人欠我儿子的钱
That clerk owed my son money.
-他是去收钱的  -他就是抢劫  乔
- He was just there to collect. - It was a robbery, Joe.
是你说的
Says you.
怎么着  你是警察  就什么都你说了算吗
And what? So--so you a cop, so you just get to win?
不行
Nah.
我就在这里告诉你
Let me tell you something. Right here.
就现在
Right now.
是我占上风
I got the power.
因为如果我告诉那些人你是个条子
Because if I tell those cats you a damn cop
他们一定宰了你
they gonna light your ass up.
那你也一样活不成
Man, they're gonna light your ass up too.
那好吧
Yeah, well.
反正我也活不成了
Since I'm gonna die anyway,
那我死之前何不图个痛快呢
I may as well get some satisfaction before I go.
坐下
Take a seat.
我还是不明白我...
Look, I still don't understand what I--
闭嘴
Shut up.
你是叫索尼娅还是伊丽莎
Is it Sonya or Elisa?
索尼娅  我叫伊丽莎  到底是怎么了
Sonya? My name is Elisa. What--what is this?
伊丽莎  你去过斯莱德酒吧吗
Elisa, you ever been to Slide Bar?
我不记得去过
No, that doesn't ring any bells.
-没有吗  -现在有印象了吗
- It doesn't? - Anything ringing now?
那是你的车  我们查了车牌
That's your car. We ran the plates, see?
你得告诉我们实情
You need to tell us what happened.
根本没什么  那就是个醉鬼
Nothing, that's just a drunk guy
-我把他送回家了  -伊丽莎
- that I gave a ride home to. - Elisa!
你不要再扯谎了  因为这个
You need to stop lying because this
就这个人  这是绑架犯罪
this right here, that's kidnapping and assault.
外加一堆一级重罪
And a couple of Class A felonies.
另外一个被绑架的是警察
The other guy they kidnapped is a cop.
-还是我朋友  -所以别兜圈子了
- And my friend. - So we're done playing.
他们在哪  到底在哪
Where are they? Where are they!
我不知道  真不知道  他没告诉我
I don't know, I don't know. He didn't tell me.
谁没告诉你
Who didn't tell you?
雷蒙多  雷蒙多·莫拉莱斯
Reimundo. Reimundo Morales.
是我认识的一个人  是他掏钱雇我做的
He's this guy that I know. He paid me to do it.
我发誓  我不知道有什么警察
I--I swear I don't know anything about a cop.
为什么雷蒙多要绑架乔·贝克
Why'd Reimundo grab Joe Baker?
雷蒙多说乔几个星期前
Reimundo said Joe jumped him
偷袭了他  偷走了他的毒品
a few weeks ago and stole his drugs,
所以他就开始跟踪他
and so he started following him.
然后他看到乔下车进了斯莱德酒吧
And then he saw Joe pull into the Slide Bar.
然后就叫我来  让我骗住他
And so he called me, and he-he told me to play him.
怎么个骗法
Play him how?
-怎么骗  -我告诉他
- Play him how!? - I told him...
我跟他说我想和他做爱
I told him I wanted to have sex with him.
所以我放了...  我在他的喝的里放了片药
So I put--I put a pill in his drink
我们和雷蒙多某个停车场见面
and we met up with Reimundo at some parking lot.
好  他们带他去哪了
Okay, where did they take him?
我不知道  我不知道  我发誓
I don't know. I don't know, I swear.
我发誓  我不知道
I don't know, I swear.
伊丽莎·罗德里格斯  你因涉嫌绑架和袭击
Elisa Rodriguez, you're being charged
被起诉  别哭了
with kidnapping and assault. Stop crying.
不
No.
你们来这已经有一阵子了
You guys have been down here for a long time.
一直很冷  没食物  没水
It's been cold. No food, no water.
我是说  你一定渴了吧
I mean, you got to be thirsty.
好了
Come on.
你就这么点本事
That's the best you can do? Hm?
说点能让我停手的
Tell me something to make me stop.
比如我的货在哪
Like where my coke is.
我不能告诉你
All right, I can't tell you
你的货在哪  因为我不知道
where your coke is because I don't know.
好吗  听我说
All right? Now, look.
不管你信不信  我说的是实话
Whether you believe me or not, I'm telling you it's the truth.
都是实话
It's the truth.
等等  等等  等一下
Wait, wait, wait a minute!
但我能告诉你点别的
But there's something I could tell you.
你需要知道的事
There's something that you need to know.
那家伙  他不是他说的那样
That man right there. He ain't who he says he is.
什么意思
What the hell you mean?
-意思就是...  - 意思就是我说谎了  兄弟
- It means-- - It means I was lying, man.
我不是什么保安  好吗
I ain't no damn security guard, a'ight?
我也是贩毒的
I deal dope, too.
好了  是我拿走了你的货
Okay, I'm the one who took your coke.
我和我的一个伙伴
It was me and one of my partners.
乔和这事没关系
Joe ain't had nothing to do with it,
但我们的确用了他的房子
but we did use his house.
好吗  好吗  就是这样
Okay? A'ight? Now, there it is.
是我干的
I did it.
-我知道你想报复  -你他妈说对了
- And I know you want payback. - You damn right.
好  这可以理解
Right. Which is understandable.
-但并不明智  -为什么
- But that's also not smart. - Why?
因为是个人都知道
Because everyone knows that money
要钱比复仇好
spends better than revenge.
拜托  兄弟
Come on, man.
好吗  让我来给你弄点大钱来  兄弟
Right? Let me get you some real money, man.
好吗
Right?
我是认真的  伙计
I'm talking about serious paper, dog.
放我们出去
Just get us up out of here.
忘记这次误会  兄弟  原谅
Forget this whole misunderstanding, man, forgive.
-我从不会原谅  -什么
- I don't do forgiveness. - What?
-我的字典里没有这两个字  -兄弟
- That ain't in my nature. - Ah, man.
拜托  兄弟  不
Come on, man, huh. Nah.
Come on, man. Nah, man.
给
Here.
这种小把戏  没用的
This little game. It ain't gonna work.
他们想杀了我们
They're gonna kill us.
迟早的事
It's just a matter of time.
不  我们不会死的  今天不会
Oh, no, we're not dying. Not today.
好吗  你就把嘴闭上  让我来想办法
Okay? Just keep your damn mouth shut and let me do this.
兄弟  听我说
Hey. Hey, yo, man, let me holler at you.
我能问你个问题吗  兄弟  你是傻还是什么
Can I ask you a question, man? You stupid or what?
你他妈说什么
What the hell you say to me?
我是说  我刚刚告诉你兄弟
I'm just saying, man, I just told your boy
我能给你们弄到一大笔钱
that I can get you a lot of money.
但那家伙没问我钱在哪  有多少钱
And instead of asking me where it is or how much
而是在我腿上钻了个洞
this man drilled a damn hole in my leg.
好吧
Okay.
多少
How much?
十万
100k.
你什么时候能弄到
When can you get it by?
你他妈给我个电话就能弄到
As soon as you get me a damn phone.
听着
Yo.
别玩我  兄弟
Don't play me, homey.
那是对我的侮辱
It's insulting.
我不会那么做的  不会对你那么做的
I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that, not to you.
十万
100k.
好吗  那可是一大笔钱  兄弟
A'ight? That's a lot of money, bro.
警长  有进展了
Hey, Sarge, we got something.
乔车库里的毒品
That brick of coke in Joe's garage.
技术队提取到一些指纹
Techs lifted some prints.
和凯尔文·希尔的指纹相匹配
They match Calvin Hill.
凯尔文·希尔  他在后院的朋友
Calvin Hill? His friend from the Y?
把他抓回来  扔到笼子里
Grab him. Put him in the cage.
有问题吗
You got a problem with that?
没有
No.
你不知道有多少次我想杀了你
You don't know how many times I thought about killing you.
我想有很多次吧
I'm guessing a lot.
我想了无数种杀你的方法
I used to think of all kind of ways of how to do it.
用球拍砸死你
Smashing you in the head with a bat.
从背后爆头
Shooting you in the back of the head.
或正面爆头
Or the face.
应该没什么差别吧
Guess it wouldn't make much difference.
但是你知道我...
But you know what I would...
我通常都会用这个方法
I would usually come back to this.
我...
Me...
掐住你的脖子
Grabbing you by the neck.
用最大的力气掐
Squeezing as hard as I could.
看着你的眼睛不再有光泽
Then watching your eyes go blank.
我在里面的时候  夜晚经常这么想
I used to think about that at night in the joint.
这是我自己的特殊的数羊的方法
It's my own little special way of counting sheep.
下周罗尼就20岁了
Ronnie would be 20 next week.
如果不是你杀了他
If it wasn't for you.
我知道
I know.
但你一点责任都没有  是吗
But none of this is on you, huh?
我
Me?
我记得罗尼  他不是个坏孩子
I remember Ronnie. He wasn't a bad kid.
直到他开始模仿他的黑帮老爸
Till he started imitating his gangbanger daddy.
我那是在教他怎么做一个男人
I was teaching him how to be a man.
你是在教他这么去死
You were teaching him how to die.
这是怎么回事
What's this?
这里就是我们和人交谈的地方  当...
This is where we talk to people when there's...
有特殊情况的时候
Special circumstances.
好吧  我不明白
Okay, I don't follow.
我们查了你的手机
Well, we dumped your phone.
找到了很多和雷蒙多·莫拉莱斯的电话
Found a lot of calls to Reimundo Morales.
你偷的那个毒贩
The drug dealer you ripped off.
挟持了你的朋友乔  和我的朋友凯文
Holding your friend Joe and my friend Kevin,
一个警察  当人质
a cop, hostage.
你看啊  乔...
See Joe...
偷东西的那天晚上他甚至都不在城里
He wasn't even in town the night of the robbery.
是的  我们和他的假释官聊过了
Yeah, we talked to his parole officer.
你知道他说什么吗
You know what he said?
他说乔在威斯康星
He said Joe was in Wisconsin.
但我想你已经知道了
But I guess you already knew that.
-我要律师  -太晚了
- I want a lawyer. - Oh, it's too late for that.
凯尔文
Calvin.
-雷蒙多住在哪  -我不知道
- Where's Reimundo live? - I don't know.
你不知道  不知道
You don't know? Don't know.
-给  接住  -天
- Here, catch. - Man.
你他妈干什么
What the hell are you doing?
是啊  我在干什么
Yeah, what am I doing?
两年前
Two years ago,
把个小痞子关在这里  关了几个小时
put some punk in here, held him for a few hours.
结果他在这偷了把枪
Turns out he snuck a gun in here.
抵住下巴
Put it under his chin.
一枪爆头
Blew the top of his head off.
枪上都是他的指纹
His finger prints were all over the gun.
-雷蒙多住哪里  -我不知道
- Where's Reimundo live? - I don't know.
好  我和一个手下抢了雷蒙多
Okay! Me and one of my boys ripped off Reimundo.
我们戴了面具  所以他不知道是我们
We wore mask so he wouldn't know it was us.
还有别人跟雷蒙多一起吗
Was Reimundo with anybody else?
有
Yeah.
好像是他的堂兄弟
I think it was his cousin.
那人叫瓦斯克兹
A guy named Vasquez.
我们抢了半块  我把它藏在了乔的车库里
We took a half a brick, and I hid it in Joe's garage.
我只知道这些
That's all I got.
我发誓
I swear, man.
拜托
Please.
把这废物抓起来
Arrest this punk.
走吧  走吧
Come on. Come on.
听说你一直在给我堂兄弟洗脑
I hear you been putting ideas in my cousin's head.
是的  但这交易真的划算
Yeah. They real good ideas though.
你想让我相信有十万
You expect me to believe 100 grand?
如果我撒谎  你会杀了我  对吗
If I'm lying, you'll kill me, right?
-你想想  -好吧  钱在哪里
- Think about it. - Okay, where's the money?
在我哥们AD那里
With my homey, A.D.
我上周给了他三块
I gave him three bricks last week.
三万五一块  你可以算算
At 35 a piece so, I mean, you do the math.
-钱在你哥们那里  -拜托
- And your boy's got the money? - Come on, man.
钱当然在他那里
Of course he's got the money.
那是我的钱
A'ight. It's my money.
听到没  所以你让我跟他打个电话
You hear me? So just let me get on the phone with him.
打吧  你要是愿意  可以全程听着
Come on, bro. You can listen to the whole conversation if you want to,
让我打个电话就行
just at least let me make the phone call.
输号码
Put in the number.
如果没人接  你死定了
If someone doesn't answer, you die.
阿特沃特已经失踪32小时了
Atwater has been missing for 32 hours.
亚当  32小时了
Adam, 32 hours.
现在还不全体出动吗
Isn't it time for all hands on deck?
可以冒这个险的啊  那可是阿特沃特
It might be worth the risk. It's Atwater.
不是我们说了算的
It's not our call.
缉毒组那边可能有人知道
Somebody in Narcos could know something.
你别再想了
You got to let it go.
-我不想停下来  -好了
- I don't want to let it go. - All right, hey.
我们得冷静一点
We got to stay cool.
-肯定没事的  -随你怎么说吧
- All right? It's gonna be fine. - Sure, whatever you say.
是我的卧底电话  可能有线索
That's my UC phone. Maybe it's a tip.
是吧
You know?
-在  -AD
- Yeah. - Hey. A.D.
AD  还好吧
A.D. What's up, man?
上周那单生意我得跟你重新谈一下
I need to renegotiate that deal from last week, man.
你能帮我这个忙吧
You can do me that solid, right?
你没事吧  一直没你消息
Hey, you cool, man? I haven't heard from you.
我没事
I'm good, okay?
仔细听我说
Just listen to what I'm saying.
上周  对吧
Last week, right?
我以三万五的价格给了你三块
I fronted you 3 bricks at about 35.
所以你那里应该有十万多  对吧
So you should be at about 105 large, right?
你现在就要那笔钱吗
You want the money now?
-是的  情况有变  -我们都谈好了
- Yeah, man, things change. - We had a deal.
我没说我要反悔
I'm not saying we don't.
我没说谈好的不算  我只是说
I'm not saying we don't have a deal, I'm just saying
我现在就要那笔钱所以
I need my money now so
下次我给你三万一块  行吗
how about next time I get you in about 30 a piece, huh?
-这样行吗  -我听到了
- How that sound? - I hear that.
所以可以吧
Okay, so we good?
我可以给你九万  也就你面子大
I can get you 90, only cause it's you.
时间地点  兄弟
When and where, bro?
是的  就是这意思
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
第95大街和毕夏普大街路口那个老工厂见
Let's meet me at that old factory on 95th and Bishop,
我派手下一个人去拿
and I'll send one of my guys to come grab that.
不不不  哥们
No, no, no, man.
必须你自己来
It's gotta be you.
我可不会把那么多钱给一个陌生人
I'm not giving that kind of cash to a stranger.
AD  只能这样
A.D. This the only way it's gonna work,
明白吗
you understand me?
所以  第95大街和毕夏普大街路口
So, 95th and Bishop.
带上钱  好吗
Bring the money, okay?
AD
A.D.
好吧  那就这样吧
All right, man, if that's how it is.
毕竟是你的钱  给我两个小时
It's your money. Give me two hours.
好兄弟  没问题
My man. Sounds good to me.
我们去哪里搞这笔钱
How are we gonna get the money?
我们又不能去找伍兹申请1505资金
We can't go to Woods for the 1505 funds.
这个交给我
Just let me worry about that.
去我地下室拿钱
Get the money from my basement.
装包里  藏个窃听器和追踪器
Put it in a bag, stitch in a listening device and a tracker.
好的
You got it.
测试  测试  窃听器能用吗
Check, check. Bag mic work?
你们能听到吧
You hear me all right?
收到  这里能听到
Copy. We got you over here, man.
看到他了
We got him.
好  火鸟来了
All right, Firebird's coming.
记住  顺利完成交易
Remember, let the exchange happen.
得让这家伙带我们去找阿特沃特
This guy's gonna lead us to Atwater.
你是AD吗
You A.D.?
你是谁
Who's asking?
安东尼的朋友
Friend of Anthony's.
你有包裹要给我吗
You got a package for me?
都在里面了
It's all there.
我可不会听你的
I ain't taken your word.
是真的
It's been real, yo.
跟安东尼说我们回见
Tell Anthony I'll see him soon.
得了  有什么意义呢
Come on, man. What's the point, huh?
就算你逃出去了  你还是被绑着
Even if you got out, you're still zip tied.
我可以用那里的破管子把拉带割断
I can cut the zip-tie with that broken pipe right there.
-你就是不肯放弃  是吧  -不放弃
- You don't give up, do you? - No, I don't.
你杀罗尼之前他有没有说什么
Ronnie say anything before you shot him?
说真的
For real, all right?
我很久之前就开始想这事
I've been thinking about this for too long.
拜托
Come on, man.
这又不能让罗尼复活
That's not gonna bring Ronnie back.
好吗  而且也不能救我们出去
Okay? And that's not gonna get us out of here.
所以  我们专注于眼前
So, let's focus on the now.
我拿到钱了  现在去找你
I got the cash. I'm coming at you.
不不  计划有变  拿着钱去埃克斯利那
No, no, change of plans. Take it over to Exley's.
待着别走  躲好
Stay there, stay hidden.
我两小时后去找你
I'll see you in a couple of hours.
-我把这里收拾一下  -好的
- I'm gonna clean up here. - You got it.
我这就过去
I'm headed that way right now.
谁知道会这么简单啊  是吧
Man, who'd have known it'd been so easy, right?
他要去朋友那里吗
He's going to a friend's place?
他不回那边了
He's not going back to the location.
所以那些人拿到了自己想要的
So these guys got what they wanted.
-他们会杀了凯文  -我们行动
- They're gonna kill Kevin. - All right, let's move in.
没有必要不要开枪
Do not shoot unless necessary.
这家伙是我们找到阿特沃特的唯一线索
This guy is our only link to Atwater.
重复  不要开枪
Repeat, do not shoot.
我被耍了  这是个陷阱
Yo, I've been made. It's a setup.
雷蒙多
让开
Get out the way!
快点
Come on!
芝加哥警察  手举起来
Chicago PD! Let's see those hands!
-快点  -该死
- Do it! - Damn it!
手举起来
Let's see your hands.
比利
Billy!
Billy.
放下武器
Drop the weapon.
-放下  -把枪放下
- Drop it. - Put the gun down.
-否则我们会开枪的  -不不不
- Drop it or we will shoot you. - No, no, no, hey, hey.
不会有人向你开枪的
No one's gonna shoot you, man.
好吗  你看
All right? There you go.
如果你把枪放下  不会有人向你开枪的
No one's gonna shoot you if you put that gun down.
我们只想跟你谈谈
We just want to talk to you.
-你跟我们谈  我们可以帮你  -去死
- You talk to us, we can help. - Go to hell!
比利
Billy, hey.
你跟我们谈  我们可以让你脱罪
You talk to us. We can make this go away.
比利
Billy.
Billy!
不
No!
5021紧急情况  疑犯向警方开枪
5021 emergency, shots fired at police.
-疑犯倒下  -他们在哪里
- Offender down. - Where are they?
-我的搭档在哪里  -3944南胡佛街
- Where's my partner? - 3944 South Hoover.
你不能死
You're not dying.
拜托
Come on, man.
我来
I got it.
-他死了  -我来  我救活他
- He's gone. - I got this, I got this.
-他死了  -我来
- He's gone. - I got this.
亚当  他死了
Adam, he's gone.
你为什么那样做  你刚杀了凯文
Why'd you do that? You just killed Kevin, man.
你说什么
What'd you say?
-你刚杀了凯文  -亚当
- You just killed Kevin! - Adam.
你为什么不打他的腿
Why couldn't you have shot him in the leg?
-亚当  不要  -他是我们唯一的线索
- Adam! No! - He was our only lead!
-亚当  -如果我打不中  他向伯吉斯开枪呢
- Adam! - What if I miss and he shoots Burgess? Then what?
他做得对  亚当  停下
It was the right call, Adam. Stop!
他做得对
It was the right call.
现在怎么办
What do we do now?
我来告诉你们怎么办
I tell you what we do now.
我们都团结一心
We all get back on the same page.
再努力查我们已有的线索  埃尔
And we double down on what we got. Al.
拿上比利的手机  定位雷蒙多的一次性手机
Grab Billy's phone, ping Reimundo's burner.
好  我们都看到凯文在有彩绘的玻璃窗前
Okay, we all saw that Kevin was near a stained glass window.
也就是说他可能在教堂里
That means he's probably in a church.
所以我们要搜索手机信号塔
So we're gonna search every damn church
-一英里范围内的每一座教堂  -好
- within a mile radius of that cell tower. - Yeah.
行动
Come on.
我们没时间了  抓紧行动
We're running out of time. Let's go.
那边
There.
这里
Here.
那边
Hey, come on. That way.
没事了  乔
We all good, Joe.
我们没事了
We good.
-等等  -我会告诉警察是他开枪打了你
- Wait. - I'll tell the cops he shot you.
你干什么
Wh--what are you doing?
你就是用这把枪杀了我儿子吗
Is this the gun you used to kill my son?
你现在是什么感觉
Well, how does it feel now, huh?
什么感觉
How does it feel?
乔
Joe.
我儿子说了什么
What did my son say?
-在你杀了他之前  -别这样  乔
- Right before you killed him dead. - Come on, Joe.
告诉我事情经过
Tell me how it went down!
告诉我
Tell me.
我在对他喊  让他停下
I was yelling at him. I told him to stop.
我让他跪下
I told him to get down.
我说"跪下"
I said, "Get down on your knees!"
但罗尼不肯
But Ronnie wouldn't do it.
他不肯  乔  他就继续跑
He wouldn't do it, Joe. He just kept on running.
然后我就继续喊
And then I just kept on screaming.
然后他就拔出了枪
And then he pulled out his gun.
他生前说的最后一句话是
Last thing that came out of his mouth was
"我不跪任何人"
"I don't get down on my knees for no man."
他拔出了枪  乔
He pulled out his gun, Joe.
-要不是...  -你确定吗
- And it was either- - Are you sure?
-拜托  -他是这么说的吗
- Come on, man. - That's what he said?
-我不会骗你的  -你确定他这么说的吗
- I wouldn't lie to you. - Are you sure that's what he said?
我不会骗你的  兄弟
I wouldn't lie to you, brother.
我不会的
I wouldn't.
你...
Are you--
拜托  乔
Come on, Joe.
我以我爱的一切发誓
On everything I love, bro.
亚当
Adam.
退下
Stand down.
退下  乔  把枪放下
Stand down. Joe, put the gun down.
没事了  对吧
We good, right?
没事了
We good.
放下枪  我们没事了
Just drop it. We all good, bro.
退下  我们没事了  对吧  乔
Stand down. We all good, right, Joe?
把枪放下
Just put the gun down.
把枪放下  伙计
Just put the gun down, man.
我们没事了
We're all right.
你的腿怎么样
How is that leg?
没那么严重  没事的
It's not that bad. It'll be okay.
警长  我们就不计较
So, Sarge, how about we give Joe a break
乔偷的毒品了行吗
on those drugs he stole?
他最后悔过了
He did come through in the end.
毒品不是乔偷的  是一个叫凯尔文·希尔的混蛋
Joe didn't steal the drugs. Some punk named Calvin Hill.
什么
What?
没错  整件事就是个误会
Yeah, whole thing was a mistake.
-我知道是谁  -是我
- I know exactly who that is. - It's me.
是啊  你好啊  妹子
Yeah, what's up, girl?
-还好你没事  是啊
- Glad you're okay. - Me too.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我去一下  给我两秒
I'll be right back. Give me two seconds.
特鲁迪  抱歉错过了你的生日
Trudy, I'm sorry I missed your birthday.
我忙着...
I was kind of in the middle--
安东尼奥
Antonio.
之前的事抱歉  伙计
I am sorry about before, man.
我真的太过分了
I was really out of line.
我...我只是太担心凯文了
I was just-I was so worried about Kev.
我们都是
We all were.
不过你那一枪真准
That was a hell of a shot though.
谢谢了
Thanks.
好啊
What's up?
是啊
Yeah, what's happening?
你还好吧
How you holding up? You all right?
我没事
Yeah, I'm cool, you know.
医生说我会没事的
Doc says I'm gonna be all right so.
说实话  我以为毒品是你偷的
I'm not gonna lie, I thought you stole the dope.
我承认是我的不对
And I ain't proud of that.
我不该那么想
I shouldn't assume that.
但是还好我想错了
But it does feel good to be wrong.
所以...
So yeah.
我真的差一点就开枪了
You got no idea how close I came to shooting you.
嗯
Yeah.
你为什么没开
Why didn't you?
因为你说的话
Because of what you said before.
罗尼的遗言
Ronnie's last words.
"我不跪任何人"
"I don't get on my knees for no man."
那是我教他的
I taught him that.
自从他小时候起
I used to drill those damn words
我就一直给他灌输那句话
in his head every day since he was a little boy.
所以他做的...
So what he did...
发生的事...
What happened...
是我的责任
That's on me.
It's on me.